studypoint.com 2019-11-17

# StudyPoint's Privacy Policy | Click to read about our privacy and data policies.

Home  >

StudyPoint Inc. ('StudyPoint', 'we', 'us') is dedicated to providing our customers and visitors ('you') valuable information on our website, www.studypoint.com ('website', 'site'). We are committed to treating any information you share with us with the utmost in respect and privacy. The following is a notice regarding our collection and usage practices of information you provide, and by submitting personal information to us using our site, you sign off on your acceptance of these policies. Please do not submit information to us using this website if you do not agree with the terms laid out below. StudyPoint has created and implemented this privacy policy as part of our commitment to protecting the personal information of our customers and visitors.

####   
What information do we collect?

On our site, we collect information that is provided to us by our visitors which may include name, email address, address, telephone number, student's name, student's grade level, how you heard about StudyPoint and potentially any other answers to other questions regarding your visit. This information is collected in order provide you with more information about our educational services or any other information you requested from us. For individuals applying to work for StudyPoint, we may also collect information that includes, but is not limited to, work history, education history, and additional contact information. Additionally, like many websites, we collect technical data which cannot be used to personally identify visitors, which may include, but is not limited to, browser information, IP address, how you found StudyPoint's site, and other statistical information. This information is collected by third parties and is used to improve the quality of our website. StudyPoint also uses cookies to store user preference information, and track website usage as well as your experience with this website. Cookies are small files that browsers put on the hard drive of visitors.

####   
What is this information used for?

The identifiable information that you provide to us is used to provide you with the information you requested about our educational services and ensure that we offer services within your geographic location. Should you choose to enroll in one of our programs, the information may also be used for billing purposes. (Note: enrolling in our tutoring programs must be done over the phone with one of our consultants. We do not accept online enrollments at this time. The consultant would be able to confirm the information that was given to us by you through the website). Occasionally, contact information that you have provided us may be used to inform you about limited-time promotions that we are offering, or other information regarding tutoring, test preparation, college applications or other related topics. This correspondence may take place via mail, email, text, or telephone. In addition, we may inform you about any new products or services that we develop in the future that we feel may be of interest to you.

####   
Is information ever shared or sold?

StudyPoint is a professional service and we take our clients' privacy seriously. None of this information will ever be sold or shared with unaffiliated third parties. We may provide identifiable information to third parties that we use for our own business purposes, such as providing you with requested information, processing payments or shipping materials.

####   
Children's Privacy

This site is not targeted towards children, nor do we have the intention of collecting any information from children under the age of 13. If information from children under the age of 13 is collected, their parent or guardian should contact us to have it removed. Please contact us by emailing the address at the bottom of this page.

####   
Opting Out of Email Correspondance

We occasionally will send emails to our customers and other individuals who provided us with their contact information. This is information that we believe may be of interest to you based on information you requested. Whenever you get an email from StudyPoint, which is from an automated source, you will always have the opportunity to opt out of future similar correspondence, in which case you will not receive any more similar email communication. For any information received via mail, receivers can opt out by calling one of our consultants and asking to be taken off the list. This is done by sharing with us your contact information, exactly as it appears on the mailing piece you received. At StudyPoint, we process multiple mailings at a time; therefore any requests to be taken off mailing lists may take 6 to 8 weeks to process. If you would like to continue receiving information from StudyPoint but need to correct or update any personal information, please call one of our consultants.

####   
Updates to this Policy

StudyPoint may make updates to this policy, in which case we will post changes on this site so that customers and visitors will be aware.

####   
Questions

If you have any questions about this policy, please contact us at [privacy@studypoint.com](mailto:privacy@studypoint.com).
